<table class="logbook">
    <!-- <tr>
        <th>Date</th>
        <td>
            Entry 
        </td>
    </tr> -->
<!-- past entries -->
<tr>
    <th>03.19.2025</th>
    <td>
        made a button and added some neighbors XD 
    </td>
</tr>

<tr>
    <th>03.12.2025</th>
    <td>
        added a <a href="theias-almanac/spring.html">spring journal!</a>
    </td>
</tr>
<tr>
        <th>03.09.2025</th>
        <td>
            set up <a href="https://github.com/biancarosa/lastfm-last-played">@biancarosa</a>'s last.fm API, so current song is (hopefully) actually current! 
        </td>
    </tr>

    <tr>
        <th>03.06.25</th>
        <td>
            figured out a way to update content from a seperate doc using AJAX! <a href="extras/ajax-tut.html">(here's the script i used)</a>
        </td>
    </tr>

    <tr>
        <th>03.04.25</th>
        <td>added a
            <a href="picrew.html">picrew</a>
            gallery with links to a few of my fave picrew! if you make one or have a favorite picrew of your own i'd love to see it (and maybe add it to the gallery!) until i can figure out a guestbook situation feel free to leave links in a comment on my profile!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <th>03.03.25</th>
        <td>made updates to home pg</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <th>03.01.25</th>
        <td>added TBR and current reads to
            <a href="books.html">bookshelves</a>
        </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <th>02.22.25</th>
        <td>
            <p>made the switch to linux on my laptop today! at first it felt too good to be true with how simple it was to set up. turns out it was, since my laptop refused to boot it after being shut down. after trying out a few different distros i ended up going with
                <a href="https://pop.system76.com/" target="_blank">pop! os</a>
                (which not only sounds cute, but actually worked!) if you're on the fence, i'd def recommend trying it out. here are some vids i watched to help me decide/switch:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n8vmXvoVjZw&t" target="_blank">
                        switching to linux: a beginner's guide
                    </a>
                </li>

                <li>
                    <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PSkFUemQ8Uw" target="_blank">
                        things to know before switching to linux
                    </a>
                </li>

                <li>
                    <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dhNLp7o5dr0" target="_blank">
                        linux on laptops
                    </a>
                </li>

                <li>
                    <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2mUI3CMjmMc" target="_blank">
                        beginner's guide to installing linux mint
                    </a>
                </li>
            </ul>

            i plan to put together a bigger list of resources i've found in my quest to improve my internet security/privacy in case they're helpful for anyone else!
        </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <th>02.18.25</th>
        <td>love it when a new hobby reveals itself to me. i used to be critical of the way that i hopped from interest to interest, always starting new projects. as I've gotten older it's become one of the things i love most about my creative process, though. everything i make is connected, and so while it might look like/feel like a million different things and ideas, its really all just one thing...me!</td>
    </tr>
</table>